The Great Pirate Era...
مونتاج
has proven to be a more tumultuous storm than the World Government expected.
شهد طفرة هائلة فاقت توقعات حكومة العالم
The figures in the eye of this relentless tempest are…
...ومن يشكّل بؤرة هذه الأحداث المفاجئة وجذب كل الأنظار
Monkey D. Luffy...
هو مونكي دي لوفي
and the Straw Hat Pirates!
وطاقم قبعة القش
To confront the furious Great Pirate Era...
من أجل مواجهة تقلّبات عصر القراصنة العظيم
fifty world leaders have come together for the Reverie...
يجتمع 50 قائدًا لعقد المؤتمر العالمي كل أربع سنوات
a quadrennial conference that will commence shortly.
المعروف باسم ليفيلي، وهو الآن على وشك البدء
Now is a time of great change.
سيشهد العصر تغيرًا جذريًا الآن
At Sea in the New World
في بحر العالم الجديد
The Fifth Emperor
الإمبراطور الخامس
I'm hungry!
أنا جائع
What's this?
ما هذه؟
Where did you get that?!
من أين أتيت بها؟
Huh? I just found it in my pocket.
سقطت من جيبي
Cool! Is it real?
مذهل! أهذا حقيقي؟
What is it?
ماذا تقصد؟
Don't you remember? It's what Germa used to transform!
أنسيت؟ جيرما يستخدمون مثل هذه للتحوّل
Oh, that's right!
!أجل، تذكرت
I'm gonna transform with it!
سأتحوّل باستخدامها
Wait! I'll go first!
مهلًا، سأستخدمها أولًا
Sanji!
سانجي
I'm gonna get rid of it!
سأتخلّص منها
Don't throw it away!
لا ترمها
If you do, I'll look for it on the ocean floor!
إن رميتها، فسأغوص إلى أعماق البحر للبحث عنها
That's impossible! You can't swim!
مستحيل، فلا تستطيع السباحة أصلًا
I found it in my pocket. If you don't want it, let me have it instead!
إن كنت لا تريدها، فأعدها إليّ بما أنها كانت في جيبي
No, let me have it! Please!
لا، بل أعطني إياها رجاءً
No way!
لا فائدة
But I wonder how it ended up in Luffy-san's pocket.
ولكن كيف وصل هذا الشيء إلى جيب لوفي-سان؟
Has to be Niji's work. He did it as a dig against me.
لا بد أنه نيجي، أظن أنه فعل هذا لإزعاجي
If I'm to get stronger, my power won't come through their brand of science!
لا أريد أن أغدو أقوى باستخدام قوتهم العلمية السخيفة
Think about it, Sanji!
لا تتسرّع يا سانجي
Science is a noble human power.
العلم يعد قوة بشرية أيضًا
Why do you care so much?!
لمَ ترغبان بها لهذه الدرجة؟
If we used the raid suit...
...إن ارتدينا البذلات القتالية
maybe we could shoot beams!
فقد نتمكن من إطلاق أشعة الليزر
Are you guys children?!
ما هذا التفكير الطفولي السخيف؟
Leave that kind of stuff to Franky! We've filled the gimmicky shipmate quota.
يكفينا وجود فرانكي عضوًا غريبًا في الطاقم
No! It's mine!
لا، أريدها
What? Were you making light of science?
ماذا؟ هل سخرت من العلم؟
Nami-swan !
!نامي-سوان
There's no way I'd insult your science!
يستحيل أن أسخر من العلم
My Sorcery Clima-Tact is the fusion of...
عصاي المناخية السحرية هي مزيج بين علم السماء
atmospheric science and Usopp’s engineering!
ومهارات أوسوب اليدوية
Look!
هيا
I just love bein' inside her tact!
كم أحب البقاء داخل العصا
Zeus?! You actually tagged along?!
هل أتيت معنا حقًا يا زيوس؟
I can't believe food outweighs your loyalty to Big Mom!
!لا أصدق أنك انسقت وراء شهوتك متخليًا عن ولائك لبيغ مام
I got myself a powerful servant!
أصبح لدي خادم قوي
N-Nami-san...
!نـ-نامي-سان
Zeus, remember this.
...تذكر قولي هذا يا زيوس
I've been serving Nami-san since long before you came along!
أنا كنت خادم نامي-سان أولًا
But I get to live in the tact she keeps under her clothes!
لكنني أعيش داخل العصا التي لا تفارق جسد نامي على الإطلاق
Sanji-san, you're arguing with water vapor.
سانجي-سان، إنه مجرد كتلة من بخار الماء
All right! Let's go!
هيا، تحوّل
Why isn't it working?!
لمَ لا تعمل؟
Stop whining!
كفاكما بكاءً
I guess it only works on you!
يبدو أنك الوحيد القادر على استخدامها
Yeah! Show us!
حاول من أجلنا
Shut up! I'm not part of Germa!
اخرسا، أنا لست من الجيرما
Listen up! "Germa 66!" "Vinsmoke!"
"اسمعا، "جيرما66" و"فينسموك
Those are two names I never want to hear again!
إياكما أن تنطقا بهذين الاسمين أمامي
Thank you!
شكرًا لك
Please transform!
تحوّل رجاءً
L-Let go of me, you morons!
أفلتاني
Hey, everybody! The newspaper's here!
وصلت الصحيفة يا رفاق
Is there anything about us?
أيوجد فيها أخبار عنّا؟
Let's see...
...لنرَ
A close-up of Luffy!
صورة لوفي؟
What about Jinbe? Does it say what happened after we left?!
ماذا عن جيمبي؟ أيوجد أخبار عمّا حدث بعد رحيلنا؟
Hmm. Jinbe, Jinbe… There's not much mentioned after we got away.
...جيمبي، جيمبي لا يوجد أي أخبار عمّا حدث بعد رحيلنا
It just says Luffy, Sanji, Jinbe, and Bege attempted to assassinate Big Mom.
كل ما ذُكر أن لوفي وسانجي وجيمبي وبيجي حاولوا اغتيال بيغ مام
And that Luffy was the mastermind!
وأن لوفي كان العقل المدبر
Mastermind?!
العقل المدبر؟
Oh, bounty posters!
!ملصقات مطلوبين
My bounty went up! It's 330 million belly!
ارتفعت مكافأتي إلى 330 مليون بيري
For real?!
أهذا حقيقي؟
Wait, what was Moss Head's at?
مهلًا، كم كانت مكافأة رأس الطحلب؟
I think Zoro-san's is...
...أظن أن مكافأة زورو-سان
320 million belly!
كانت 320 مليون بيري
Yes!
!مرحى
Beat that, damn Moss Head!
تفوقت عليك يا رأس الطحلب اللعين
It's just a number.
!كل هذا من أجل مجرّد رقم
They changed "only alive" back to "dead or alive"!
"لقد غيروا "على قيد الحياة" إلى "حيًا" أو "ميتًا
Huh? What's wrong?
عجبًا، ما الخطب؟
My name...
...اسمي
It says "Vinsmoke Sanji"!
"مكتوب "فينسموك سانجي
Makes sense.
فهمت
GLOOM...
...إحباط
My bounty only increased because of Germa's infamy!
ارتفعت مكافأتي بسبب سمعة جيرما السيئة
S-Sanji-san ! Are you okay?!
هل أنت بخير يا سانجي-سان؟
Huh! There's an even gloomier aura coming from there!
يا للهول، أشعر بهالة أكثر إحباطًا من هناك
GLOOM...
...إحباط
DOOM...
...الكآبة
L-Luffy!
!لوفي
GLOOM...
...إحباط
DOOM...
...الكآبة
What's wrong?!
ما الخطب؟
Meanwhile...
...وفي هذه الأثناء
The world is abuzz with talk of the Reverie, the global summit...
يترقّب الناس اجتماع قادة العالم في مؤتمر ليفيلي
held every four years in the Holy Land of Mary Geoise.
الذي يُعقد مرة كل 4 سنوات على الأرض المقدسة ماريجوا
This is Fishman Island, 10,000 meters below sea level.
وعلى جزيرة البرمائيين التي تقبع بعمق 10 آلاف متر تحت سطح البحر
The Ryugu Kingdom.
مملكة ريوغو
He did it-jamon !
لقد فعلوها
Jinbe finally joined Luffy-kun's crew!
انضم جيمبي إلى طاقم لوفي أخيرًا
It's unbelievable to think the two of them picked a fight with Big Mom.
...لكنني لا أصدق أنهما قررا خوض معركة ضد بيغ مام
King Neptune Ryugu Kingdom
ممكلة ريوغو الملك نبتون
I wonder if they escaped on the same ship.
هل هرب جيمبي وقبعة القش على متن السفينة نفسها يا تُرى؟
Manboshi
مانبوشي
Ryuboshi
ريوبوشي
Jinbe and Straw Hat-fa-so-la-ti-do !
~جينبي وقبعة القش فا-سو-لا-تي-دو
Fukaboshi
فوكابوشي
Of course they did. The article says Big Mom was furious.
بلا شك، فالصحيفة تُشير إلى أن بيغ مام غاضبة للغاية
We need to officially declare that our country is now under the Straw Hats' protection-jamon !
بهذه الحالة، يجب أن تكون هذه الجزيرة تحت حماية طاقم قبعة القش من الآن فصاعدًا
Father! Brothers!
أبي، إخوتي
Shirahoshi!
شيراهوشي
Princess Shirahoshi
الأميرة شيراهوشي
I'll go to the Reverie with you!
سأرافقكم إلى الليفيلي
I have to go, or Luffy-sama will call me Wimpyhoshi again!
وإلّا فسيناديني لوفي-ساما بالضعيفة مجددًا
I've been waiting for you to come around!
كنا ننتظركِ تقولين ذلك
All right, let's go!
حسنٌ، هيا بنا
Okay!
أجل
However, overshadowing the upcoming Reverie and stunning the public was the news that rookie pirate...
ولكن، ما جذب انتباه الناس أكثر من الاجتماع الوشيك هي الأخبار المتعلقة باليونكو بيغ مام والقرصان الشاب
Straw Hat Luffy threatened Emperor Big Mom, whose position hadn't wavered in decades.
قبعة القش لوفي الذي أدهش الجميع أنْ تحدّاها وقوتها التي لم تهتز منذ عقود
The article stated the following:
:ذُكر في مقال الصحيفة التالي
"A reliable source has confirmed that Straw Hat Luffy...
وفقًا لمصدر موثوق، قبعة القش لوفي
has already taken command of seven other powerful pirate crews.
يملك تحت رايته 7 طواقم قراصنة قوية
This move makes him the commander of 5,000 subordinates.
بالإضافة إلى أسطولٍ يتضمّن 5000 تابع مما يجعله قائدًا عظيمًا
Of note, both Ace and the Revolutionary Army's number two, Sabo,
سوء سمعته لم تعد ناجمة من كونه أخ ايس فحسب بل أيضًا لكونه أخ سابو
are considered his sworn brothers.
الذي يعد نائب قائد الجيش الثوري
He convinced the evil army Germa 66,
جيش الشر جيرما 66
the Sun Pirates, and the Fire Tank Pirates to follow him...
وطاقم قراصنة الشمس وطاقم قراصنة فاير تانك ...جميعهم أجبروا على الخضوع إليه
without hesitation, all due to his leadership and charisma.
بسبب جاذبية شخصيته وقيادته الاستثنائية
His guileful strategy resulted in the destruction of the queen's castle.
أسفرت خطته العبقرية عن تدمير قصر الملكة
His might brought down two of her commanders, worth 800 million and one billion respectively.
كما أنه هزم اثنان من قادة الحلوى تبلغ مكافأت أحدهما مليار والآخر 800 مليون بيري
Therefore, it is natural to consider Straw Hat Luffy the victor!"
لذا من الواضح للعيان أن قبعة القش لوفي انتصر في المعركة
And so, the article concludes with a proclamation:
:ويخلص المقال إلى نتيجة مفادها
"The fifth emperor has emerged!"
ظهور الإمبراطور الخامس
What's all this "fifth emperor" garbage?!
ما هذا الهراء حول "الإمبراطور الخامس"؟
It's just more pirate scum causing trouble,
لن تفيدكم ألقاب سخيفة كالأباطرة الأربعة أو الخمسة أيها القراصنة الأوغاد
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki Navy Headquarters
مقر البحرية أدميرال الأسطول ساكازوكي
I have a report for you, Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
بلغنا تقرير يا أدميرال الأسطول ساكازوكي
En route to the Reverie,
ثمة قراصنة هاجموا سفينة مملكة لولوشيا المتجهة إلى الليفيلي
The king was unharmed, but Princess Comane has been kidnapped.
الملك بخير، لكن الأميرة كوماني قد خُطفت
What was the naval escort doing?!
ما فائدة دوريات الحراسة؟
Check.
كش
Grandfather! Grandfather!
جدي
Hmm? What is it, Rebecca?
ما الخطب يا ريبيكا؟
Look!
انظر
“Assassins Make Attempt on Big Mom's Life"
محاولة اغتيال بيغ مام
Have you read the news about Lucy?!
هل قرأت الأخبار المتعلقة بلوسي؟
Rebecca A Dressrosan Lady-in-Waiting
ولية عهد مملكة دريسروزا: ريبيكا
Yes, I have.
أجل، قرأتها
Luffyland is amazing! That's our boss for you!
لوفيلاند مُذهل، كما هو متوقع من زعيمنا
The article mentioned us too.
ذكرتنا الصحف أيضًا
Commander Leo Tonta Corps Tontatta Tribe
:قائد قوات تونتا من قبيلة تونتاتا ليو
Everyone, once we reach the Holy Land, you must not talk about this.
إياكم ذكر هذه الأمور حالما ندخل الأرض المقدسة
What? Why not?
ماذا؟ لماذا؟
We may be indebted to him,
صحيح أننا ندين له بالكثير
but the World Government and the Navy see him differently.
لكن حكومة العالم والبحرية لديهما رأي آخر عنه
You're right! He's a pirate!
معك حق، إنه قرصان
Exactly. And he's now gaining an extraordinarily dangerous reputation.
كما أنه سيعد شخصًا خطرًا للغاية من الآن فصاعدًا
He's really something. Oh yeah! I've got to show Viola-san !
!إنه مذهل فعلًا تذكرت، سأريها لفيولا-سان
Let's do that!
لنذهب
No mistaking it. Those ships belong to the Kingdoms of Dressrosa and Prodence!
لا شك في ذلك، إنها سُفن مملكتي دريسروزا وبرودينس
And no naval escort!
ولا أثر لدوريات حراسة البحرية
Oh! I-I see Princess Viola!
إنني أرى الأميرة فيولا
She's as gorgeous as they say.
آية في الجمال كما شيع عنها
Is that other girl a member of the royal family?
هل الفتاة بجانبها من العائلة الملكية أيضًا؟
We'll get to name our price if we kidnap the both of 'em too.
كم سيدفعون لنا فديةً إن خطفناهما يا تُرى؟
Right, Princess Comane?
ما رأيكِ أيتها الأميرة كوماني؟
Just call Papa already! He'll pay you as much as you want!
اتصلوا بأبي بسرعة، سيدفع لكم ما تشاؤون
This is why I like royal families!
لهذا السبب أحب العوائل الملكية
Just hold out a bit longer. We're pretty damn greedy.
ولكن عليكِ الانتظار قليلًا، فنحن جشعون
Anyway, they won't see us coming...
...لن يلاحظوا وجودنا
since we're hidden underwater!
لأننا نختبئ تحت الماء
Sink 'em!
أغرقهم
Roger!
عُلم
It's impossible to guard against a torpedo!
يستحيل التصدي لهذه القذيفة
What?!
ما الأمر؟
An ambush?!
هجوم عدو؟
Ready the cannons!
جهزوا المدافع
Yes, sir!
حاضر
Don't! There's no need!
لا داعي، اطمئنوا
I'm glad I made it in time! You're safe now!
يُسعدني أنني وصلت في الوقت المناسب، أنتم بأمان الآن
Y-You're with the Navy?
أأنت جندي بحرية؟
"Justice"
العدالة
Captain Koby Navy Headquarters
عقيد في قوّات البحرية كوبي
I'm Captain Koby of Navy Headquarters!
أنا كوبي، عقيد في قوّات البحرية
Did we miss the target?!
هل أخطأت الهدف؟
That's impossible!
!مستحيل
We're gonna sink!
سنغرق
You're not hurt, are you?
لم تتأذوا، صحيح؟
Your parties are from Dressrosa and Prodence, right? You must be tired from your long journey.
إنكم الوفد المشارك من مملكتي دريسروزا وبرودينس، صحيح؟ لا بد أنكم مرهقون من رحلتكم الطويلة
What just happened? How did you get here?
ماذا حدث للتو؟ كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
I had to go on ahead of my ship.
أتيتُ من سفينة بحرية بعيدة
Just now, pirates were targeting you from underwater.
هاجمت سفينتكم للتو قراصنة مختبئون تحت البحر
"Underwater"? You mean by torpedo?!
تحت البحر؟ أتقصد قذيفة؟
I'm glad they missed!
من الجيد أنها لم تُصبنا
Me too.
أجل
Helmeppo-san! Report!
ما الوضع عندك يا هيلميبو-سان؟
We caught the pirates!
قبضنا على القراصنة
Look!
انظروا
Princess Comane from Lulucia is okay too!
الأميرة كوماني من مملكة لولوشيا بخير أيضًا
Lieutenant Commander Helmeppo Navy Headquarters
رائد في قوّات البحرية هيلميبو
Why you little...!
هؤلاء الأوغاد
Skewer them alive and roast them to a crisp! They need to pay!
ينبغي حرقهم وسلخهم، لن أسامحهم
Of course, they'll be punished accordingly, Princess!
سيدفعون ثمن فعلتهم بالطبع يا سمو الأميرة
Anyway, how is your observation haki so advanced, Koby?!
ولكن كيف لهاكي التنبؤ لديك أن يكون بهذه الدقّة يا كوبي؟
I never even sensed the torpedo.
فلم أشعر بالقذيفة إطلاقًا
A submarine?
غواصة؟
Pirates these days necessitate caution from all. That was close.
ينبغي الحذر من قراصنة هذه الأيام، كان ذلك خطرًا
You!
أنت
So, you're the famous Captain Koby!
لا بد أنك العقيد الشهير كوبي
What? From the Rocky Port Incident?
ماذا؟ من حادثة الميناء الصخري؟
Trafalgar Law, one of the Worst Generation, played a pivotal role in that incident.
الحادثة التي كان خلفها ترافالغار لاو؛ أحد أفراد الجيل الأسوأ
You're the hero who protected the citizens.
أنت البطل الذي حمى المواطنين آنذاك
N-No, I'm no hero!
لا تلقبني بالبطل رجاءً
You're not just brave, you're a fine young man!
لم أتوقع أن ذلك البطل الشجاع هو مجرّد شاب
Wow, he looks tough.
!يبدو هذا الشخص قويًا
He just saved us from a torpedo, yet he doesn't want any credit?
لم يتفاخر بإنقاذنا من القذيفة التي كانت موجهة إلينا
Thank you!
شكرًا لك
Oh, no...
لا داعي
Oh! Luffy-san !
!لوفي-سان
I mean, it's Straw Hat Luffy! The front-page article caught my eye.
لا، بل أقصد قبعة القش لوفي الصفحة الرئيسية في الصحيفة قد لفتت انتباهي
Do you wanna read it, Koby-san ?
أتودّ قراءتها يا كوبي-سان؟
No, no. Well, I mean, you know...
...لا.. حسنٌ.. أعني.. عفوًا
"The fifth emperor."
"إمبراطور البحر الخامس"
Luffy-san's still as cool as ever!
لوفي-سان رائع كالعادة
He keeps moving forward!
إنه يواصل المضي قدمًا
Koby-san ?
كوبي-سان؟
Every time I see you in the paper, I think back to that day.
...تراودني ذكريات ذلك اليوم كلما رأيتك تتصدر عناوين الصُحف
Hey, Captain Koby! What are you doing? Come back already!
ما الذي تفعله أيها الرائد كوبي؟ عُد إلى هنا
Right!
أجل
Thank you so much!
شكرًا جزيلًا لكِ
Sure.
العفو
Seeing how close we are to New Marineford,
ستصلون إلى المارينفورد الجديدة قريبًا
allow us to escort you the rest of the way!
لذا سنرافقكم لضمان وصولكم بأمان
I give you my thanks.
شكرًا لكم
Oh, hey!
...أخبرني
What is it?
ما الأمر؟
Do you like Lucy, Koby-kun ?
أتحب لوسي يا كوبي-كن؟
You like Luffyland, right?
تحب لوفيلاند، صحيح؟
N-No! H-He's my enemy!
لا، إنه عدونا
Can't fool us!
قل الصراحة
We won't tell.
...لن نخبر أحدًا
Stay and chat.
لنتحدث قليلًا
K-Kindly let go! I-I'm with the Navy!
دعيني رجاءً، أنا من البحرية
But you looked so happy when you read the paper.
لكنك بدوت سعيدًا حين قرأت الصحيفة
Th-That's because...
...ذلك بسبب
Come on. Let's talk!
أخبرنا هيا
P-Please stop!
توقفي رجاءً
Oh, Luffyland is in this article here too!
لوفيلاند مذكور في هذه المقالة أيضًا
He is?!
ماذا؟
So you do like him!
أنت تحبه فعلًا
Damn.
سحقًا
Having my bounty increase because of Germa's reputation...
ارتفعت مكافأتي بسبب اسم الجيرما
is so depressing.
يا للإحباط
Hey, are you all right?
مهلًا، هل أنت بخير؟
Do your wounds hurt?
أتؤلمك جراحك؟
N-No.
...لا
My...
...بل هذا
My bounty went down!
مكافأتي انخفضت
Look... it's 150 million belly!
انظروا، أصبحت 150 مليون بيري
Really?! I thought it just increased to 500 million recently!
حقًا؟ ظننتُها ارتفعت إلى 500 مليون منذ وقت قريب
One hundred fifty million is lower than your bounty two years ago!
إن 150 مليون أقل حتى من مكافأتك قبل سنتين
How is that even possible?! Did you do something wrong?!
أيعقل هذا؟ هل فعلت شيئًا سيئًا؟
Wouldn't that make it bigger?
ألن ترتفع بذلك؟
Oh, that's right.
أجل، بالفعل
It's not so bad. Fewer people will come after us.
لا بأس، فلن يسعى الناس خلفك
Nami-san ! Luffy is our captain! This could harm our whole image!
!لوفي قائدنا يا نامي-سان لذا قد يقلل ذلك من هيبتنا
This sucks! Why?!
سحقًا، لماذا؟
A Port Town Kingdom of Lulucia Grand Line
الغراند لاين بلدة ساحلية في مملكة لولوشيا
Prepare the cannons!
استعدوا للإطلاق
Fire at will!
!نار
Let's go!
هيا بنا
Grab their money and valuables!
اسلبوا كل أموالهم وبضاعتهم
Where's the Navy?!
ما الذي تفعله البحرية؟
Didn't they already arrive to help?!
حسبتهم أتوا لإنقاذنا
They destroyed our ship!
كيف تجرؤ على تدمير سفينتنا؟
Damn!
!سحقًا
To hell with the Navy!
عن أي بحرية تتحدثون؟
Their king's gone to the Reverie. All their best soldiers went away with him!
ذهب ملكهم إلى الليفيليي وبرفقته نخبة الجنود
A defenseless country is jus' beggin' pirates to raid it!
البلاد التي تفتقر للحراسة تُعد هدفًا سهلًا للقراصنة
Now listen good!
اصغوا إليّ بعناية
I work for Blackbeard, one of the Four Emperors.
أنا تابع اليونكو اللحية السوداء
I've since been dubbed Pinkbeard!
الذي لقبني باللحية الوردية بنفسه
Captain Pinkbeard Pinkbeard Pirates Bounty: 52 Million Belly
:قائد قراصنة اللحية الوردية اللحية الوردية المكافأة: 52 مليون بيري
Captain Pinkbeard Pinkbeard Pirates Bounty: 52 Million Belly
:قائد قراصنة اللحية الوردية اللحية الوردية المكافأة: 52 مليون بيري
Remember my name!
تذكروا اسمي
Fear Blackbeard!
هابوا اللحية السوداء
All right, men! In the name of Blackbeard, take everything!
والآن يا رجال، أنهبوا منهم كل شيء باسم اللحية السوداء
Okay, hand over your money!
هيا، سلمني مالك
P-Please stop!
توقف رجاءً
It's no use hidin'! We'll burn down the whole town!
لا جدوى من الاختباء، فسنحرق البلدة بأكملها
Hey, come on! Let's get out of here!
تماسكي، لنهرب حالًا
Hey, catch that girl!
أنتما، لا تدعا تلك الفتاة تهرب
End of the line!
توقفي مكانك
What's that in your arms?
ماذا تحملين بين يديكِ؟
Whatever it is you're holdin' tight, hand it over!
أريني ما الذي تتمسكين به بشدة
This is...
...إنه
Wait, it's jus' milk?! And here I thought it was money.
ماذا؟ مجرد حليب؟ تبًا، ظننته مالًا
Screw it! I'll take it anyway.
ولكنني سآخذه
You can't! This is for the village children!
لا، إنه لأطفال القرية
Put a sock in it!
اخرسي
You're bein' awful obstinate 'bout this!
لماذا لم تسلميني إياه ببساطة؟
Please give it back!
أعده رجاءً
You see, we really need that milk!
أنا بأمس الحاجة لهذا الحليب
Bring us your money, then!
أحضري إلينا مالكِ إذن
What? I don't have any.
ماذا؟ لا أملك مالًا
I bet you have a heavenly tribute fund.
لا بد أنكم تحتفظون بأموال الجزية السماوية
Th-The heavenly tribute is what we have to pay to the king and the Celestial Dragons.
الجزية السماوية هي ضريبة ندفعها للملك والتنانين السماوية
It's all we can do to scrimp and save every day!
...إننا نقتصد وندخر المال يوميًا
If we don't pay the heavenly tribute, we'll be killed!
لأننا سنُقتل إن لم ندفع الجزية السماوية
What?! Your king sounds terrible!
ماذا؟ يبدو أن ملك بلادكم طاغية
Well, alright!
حسنٌ، فهمت
Hey, men, get searchin'! They're hidin' the heavenly tribute!
فتشوا البلدة يا رجال إنهم يخبئون الجزية السماوية في مكانٍ ما
There's money stashed away! Take all they've got!
لديهم المال، اسلبوا كل ممتلكاتهم
But why?!
لـ-لا يعقل
C'mon! Tell us where the tribute is!
هيا، أخبرني بمكان الجزية
Leave us alone. This town is poor.
ارحمونا، هذه البلدة فقيرة للغاية
P-Please, anything but this money!
لا تأخذ هذا المال رجاءً
Let go!
أفلته
Somebody...
النجدة
You wouldn't have gotten hurt if you'd jus' given up!
ما كنا سنؤذيكم لو سلمتم أموالكم بسرعة
Kill anyone who resists!
اقتلوا كل من يُخالف الأوامر
I'm begging you!
أتوسل إليك
Please just leave us alone!
أرجوك دعنا وشأننا
Shut up!
اخرسي
Go, Morley!
انطلق يا مورلي
Who the hell are you?
من أنتِ؟
Why's it shakin'?
ما هذه الهزة؟
Is there somethin' underground?!
أيوجد شيء تحت الأرض؟
The hell?!
ما هذا؟
A giant trident?!
رمح ثلاثي ضخم؟
Is that a giant?
أهو عملاق؟
One, two! One, two!
واحد، اثنان، واحد، اثنان
One, two!
واحد، اثنان
A giant just climbed straight outta the ground!
!ظهر عملاقٌ من تحت الأرض
And he's dressed really weird!
كما أنه يرتدي ملابسًا غريبة
Um, why is he wearing a miniskirt?
لمَ يرتدي تنورة قصيرة؟
Gross! Just where do you think you're looking?!
ويحكم، إلى أين تنظرون؟
Why are you staring at me?!
لمَ تحدق بي؟
Do you have a crush on me or something?!
هل أنت مُعجب بي؟
Are you kiddin' me ?! What's this dirty ol' man's deal?!
ما هذا الاتهام المُفاجئ؟ عمَ يتحدث هذا العجوز؟
Jus' shoot 'im! Shoot 'im dead!
على كلٍّ، أطلقوا عليه واقتلوه
Stop fawning over me, sillies!
توقفوا أيها الفتيان
D-Do giants live underground?!
هل يعيش العمالقة تحت الأرض؟
First one I've ever seen.
!هذه أول مرة أرى أحدهم
Who is he anyway?
من هو؟
Don't be so mean!
كفاكم لؤمًا
Come on!
بحقكم
How's this possible?! He's pushin' the ground around like clay!
كيف يعقل هذا؟ إنه يحرّك الأرض ويشكّلها كأنها طين
Don't waver! It's just a devil fruit power!
لا تذعروا، لا بد أنه مستخدم قدرة
Incredible!
!مُذهل
What'll you do now?
إذن، ماذا ستفعلون؟
You servile...
...أيها العاجزون
pieces of trash.
الحثالة
What? Trash?
حثالة؟
What should we do?
ماذا عسانا نفعل؟
Excuse me!
المعذرة
Who are... Who are you people?
من أنتِ؟ من أنتم؟
Oh, my!
لا
C'mon now! Hold off a moment, Morley!
مهلًا، انتظر قليلًا يا مورلي
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I wanted to try out my latest invention, but you jumped the gun!
أردتُ تجربة اختراعي الجديد، لكنك سبقتني
Who are these people?!
من هؤلاء؟
A murder of crows?!
سرب غربان؟
Captain!
أيها القائد
Huh?!
ثمة أحدٌ على السطح
What?!
ماذا؟
The crows are gathering!
!الغربان تتجمع
How dare you hurt those who offer no resistance.
كيف تجرؤون على مهاجمة مواطنين أبرياء؟
Captain Pinkbeard... those four...
...أيها القائد اللحية الوردية، أعرف هؤلاء الأربعة
They're usually scattered around the world!
يُفترض أنهم منتشرون حول العالم
They're the commanders...
...إنهم قادة
of the Revolutionary Army!
الجيش الثوري
W... W...
...ما...ما
Whaaat?!
ماذا؟
Commander Morley Eastern Division Revolutionary Army
مورلي قائد القوات الغربية للجيش الثوري
Hey, they're still staring at me.
مهلًا، ما زالوا يحدقون بي
Commander Belo Betty Western Division Revolutionary Army
بيلو بيتي قائدة القوات الشرقية للجيش الثوري
Keep it down, trash!
لا تذعروا أيها الحثالة
Commander Lindbergh Southern Division Revolutionary Army
ليندبريغ قائد القوات الجنوبية للجيش الثوري
Allow me to test my new weapon!
دعوني استخدم سلاحي الجديد
Commander Karasu Northern Division Revolutionary Army
كاراسو قائد القوات الشمالية للجيش الثوري
This will not go your way.
أتينا لردعكم
The commanders of...
...قادة
the Revolutionary Army?
الجيش الثوري؟
Officer Emporio Ivankov Revolutionary Army
ضابط أعلى في الجيش الثوري إمبوريو إيفانكوف
That Straw-boy sure iss somethingk!
!الفتى قبعة القش مُذهل
He certainly hass your blood.
كما هو متوقع من ابنك
Commander-in-Chief Monkey D. Dragon Revolutionary Army
قائد الجيش الثوري مونكي دي دراغون
And...
...وأيضًا
who knew that Sanji-boy vass a Germa 66 prince?!
لم أعرف أن الفتى سانجي هو أمير جيرما 66
He never spoke a voord of eet to me! Vhaat a rascal!
لم يخبرني بذلك إطلاقًا، يا لوقاحته
This debacle led to Germa's expulsion from the World Government.
طُردت جيرما من حكومة العالم إثر تلك الحادثة
Thiss iss expected of Straw-boy and Sanji-boy.
كان الفتى قبعة القش والفتى سانجي عند توقعي تمامًا
They are headliningk the Great Pirate Era!
أصبحا محط الانتباه في عصر القراصنة العظيم
Officer Inazuma Revolutionary Army
ضابط أعلى في الجيش الثوري إينازوما
The Straw Hats... Vhaat an excitingk bunch!
طاقم قبعة القش، أنا متشوّق
Hack A Revolutionary Army Soldier
جندي في الجيش الثوري هاك
Anyway, the commanders are late.
على أيّ حال، لقد تأخر كبار القادة
Koala Assistant Fishman Karate Instructor Revolutionary Army
مدربة مساعدة كاراتيه البرمائيين في جيش الثوار كوالا
Koala Assistant Fishman Karate Instructor Revolutionary Army
مدربة مساعدة كاراتيه البرمائيين في جيش الثوار كوالا
They should have arrived by now.
يُفترض أنهم وصلوا الآن
That iss true.
معكِ حق
By the vayy, Sabo, vhaat een the voorld are you doingk?
بالمناسبة يا سابو، ما الذي تفعله عندك منذ فترة؟
You've been grinning ever since reading about Luffy-kun,
أنت تواصل النظر لمقال لوفي وتبتسم
and your face cramped up, am I right?
لدرجة أن وجهك أُصيب بتشنج، صحيح؟
Vhaat a dum-dum!
أأنت أحمق؟
This is Lindbergh!
معك ليندبرغ
What's wrong? Everyone's waiting.
ما الخطب؟ الجميع ينتظركم
Is this Sabo? We're almost there.
...أهذا أنت يا سابو؟ كدنا نصل
But we ran into some trouble! Mind if we're a bit late?
ولكن طرأت مشكلة، هل تمانع إن تأخرنا قليلًا؟
Got it. Just stay in one piece.
لا مانع، مادام ستكونون بخير
Oh, I'm so excited! All the Revolutionary Army officers will be here!
هذا مشوّق، سيحضر جميع قادة الجيش الثوري إلى هنا
I get to see Morley-sama !
أتطلّع شوقًا لرؤية مورلي-ساما
I love Betty-sama by far the most!
إنني أفضّل بيتي-ساما
Sabo, the clock is ticking. We need to start.
الوقت يُداهمنا يا سابو، لنبدأ اجتماعنا الآن
Best finish the plan before they get here.
يجدر بنا إحكام خطتنا قبل وصولهم
You're up, Chief of Staff.
حان دورك يا رئيس الأركان
Yeah.
أجل
At the upcoming Reverie, we'll finally...
...في مؤتمر ليفيلي المقبل، حان الوقت أخيرًا
...declare war...
...لإعلان الحرب
Chief of Staff Sabo Revolutionary Army
رئيس أركان الجيش الثوري سابو
against the Celestial Dragons.
على التنانين السماوية
So they're...
...هؤلاء هم
the commanders of...
...قادة
the Revolutionary Army!
الجيش الثوري
Why are four of their officers here?!
لمَ القادة الأربعة هنا؟
Gosh, you boys play rough!
إنكم عنيفون يا أولاد
It's because they're falling for you, you giant lug!
ربما لأنهم معجبون بك أيها العملاق البليد
No way. That's icky!
مُحال، هذا مقزز
I checked in with Sabo! Shall we begin, Betty?!
تواصلت مع سابو للتو، لذا أيمكننا فعلها الآن يا بيتي؟
There's no stopping me.
...لستم ندًا لي
Looks like they won't answer my question. And what's that guy mumbling over there?!
لا أحد يُجيب عن أسئلتي وبماذا يتمتم ذلك الشخص؟
I deem your actions unforgivable !
!لن أغفر لهم
Why's he so pissed?!
لماذا هو غاضب؟
What's it gonna be, you human refuse?!
والآن، ماذا ستفعلون أيها الحثالة؟
Will you die? Or will you fight ?!
أتلقون حتفكم أم تقاتلون؟
Only you decide your fate!
حددوا مصيركم بأنفسكم
Why wait for a hero to come?!
أهذه مسؤولية الأبطال فحسب؟
You could be heroes!
ربما أنتم الأبطال
The townspeople picked up sticks! C'mon! Don't make me laugh!
سكان هذه البلدة محض جبناء، لا تضحكيني
Are you gonna fight us?!
هل ستقاتلونا؟
I don't know why, but I'm inspired and feel a surge of energy!
أجهل السبب، ولكنني أشعر بإلهام وقوة تتدفق بجسدي
Let's drive these pirates out of here!
لنطرد القراصنة من هنا
We should fight to protect our country!
يجب أن نقاتل لحماية بلادنا
That's right!
هذا صحيح
This is the power of Betty's Rally Rally Fruit!
هذه قدرة فاكهة بيتي كوبو-كوبو
By waving her flag, she can awaken the latent power in anyone!
يمكنها إيقاظ القوة الكامنة في الناس بالتلويح بعلمها
Betty is the flag-bearer of freedom!
بيتي حاملة راية الحرية
Now, charge!
والآن، تقدموا
It's time they learned that gettin' shot is gonna hurt!
أظنهم لا يدركون مدى ضرر تلقي رصاصة
Gotta stop while you're ahead!
لا تغتروا بأنفسكم
Lind! Karasu! Back them up!
ادعموهم يا ليند وكاراسو
Got it!
دعي الأمر لنا
Take this!
خذوا هذه
Cool Shooter!
الرشاش البارد
That's cold!
إنه ثلج
My gun just got frozen!
!تجمّد سلاحي
You rotten bastards! Get out of here, you pirates!
اخرجوا أيها القراصنة الأوغاد
Don't waver! Cut 'em down!
لا تتراجعوا، قطعوهم
Take their weapons!
اسلبوا أسلحتهم
The crows took our swords!
أخذت الغربان سيوفنا
Give 'em back!
أعيديها
Don't stop!
لا تتوقفوا
Fight! Don't give in to fate!
قاتلوا لتحديد مصيركم
Get lost!
اخرجوا
What's gotten into 'em all of a sudden?!
ماذا حدث لهم فجأة؟
Give...
...أيها اللعين
my milk...
...أعد إلي
back!
!الحليب
Let's scram!
لنهرب
This isn't over!
ستندمون
Pinkbeard... has a bounty of 52 million.
اللحية الوردية، مكافأته 52 مليون
Blackbeard-sama will come after you.
سينتقم اللحية السوداء لنا
Unfortunately for you, that man cares little for his men.
للأسف، إنه لا يكترث بشأن أتباعه
Hey, boy! Shut your pie hole already!
كفى يا ولد، اخرس
Hey, you yellow-bellied, weak-kneed, pathetic clowns!
اسمعوا أيها الجبناء الضعفاء الحثالة
If you turn him in to the World Government, you can claim his bounty.
إن سلمتموه إلى حكومة العالم، فستحصلون على المكافأة
That's 52 million belly.
إنها تبلغ 52 مليون بيري
And it's...
وهي
all yours!
من حقكم
Also, I want you to have this.
خذوا هذه أيضًا
Use this to contact the Revolutionary Army.
إنها معلومات الاتصال بالجيش الثوري
You did great today!
أبليتم حسنًا
Call us any time.
اتصلوا بنا بأي وقت
When the weak decide to make a stand, we'll come give them the push they need.
لن نتخلّى عن ضعفاء أظهروا روح المقاومة
B-Belo Betty-sama !
بيلو بيتي-ساما
Thank you for everything, Revolutionary Army!
شكرًا جزيلًا لكم أيها الجيش الثوري
Hey, what are we meeting up for this time?
بالمناسبة، ما سبب اجتماعنا هذه المرة؟
We're gonna pick a fight with the Celestial Dragons.
سنشن الحرب على التنانين السماوية
Oh, that's the best news ever! I can't wait!
عظيم، أنا متشوق
Oh, and Karasu!
بالمناسبة يا كاراسو
Turn on your voice amplifier.
اضغط زر تشغيل مكبر صوتك
I forgot.
نسيته
The Reverie begins in two more days.
تبقى يومان على انعقاد مؤتمر ليفيلي
All the pieces from around the world are beginning to coalesce.
وكل المخططات المختلفة في أنحاء العالم بدأت تتداخل حول هذا المؤتمر
Okay, roger that.
حسنٌ، مفهوم
That was the others, Sabo-kun.
تلقيتُ اتصالًا يا سابو-كن
They'll arrive shortly.
سيصل الجميع قريبًا
All right!
حسنٌ
Let's do this!
...هيا بنا
What the hell?!
ماذا يجري؟
So that punk who screwed up my valuable SMILE trade deal...
...لمَ هذا الفتى الذي أفسد تجارتي المهمة في السمايل
Kaido, "King of the Beasts" One of the Four Emperors
:أحد الأباطرة الأربعة ملك الوحوش كايدو
was in that old hag's territory?!
موجود في منطقة تلك العجوز الشمطاء؟
He's the victor?!
انتصر؟
Huh?! When exactly did I lose?!
متى خسرتُ أنا؟ وضد من؟
It was him, Mama! He printed this article!
لا بد أنه من كتب المقالة يا ماما
Oh, you'll pay for this, Morgans... No!
أجل، سأنال منك يا مورغانز...لا
The one who'll really pay...
...بل سأنال منك
Charlotte "Big Mom" Linlin One of the Four Emperors
:أحد الأباطرة الأربعة شارلوت لينلين، بيغ مام
is Straw Hat!
يا قبعة القش
An emperor?
إمبراطور؟
Marshall D. "Blackbeard" Teach One of the Four Emperors
:أحد الأباطرة الأربعة اللحية السوداء مارشال دي تيتش
It's a bit premature to call you that!
ما زال هذا اللقب مبكرًا عليك
"Red-Haired" Shanks One of the Four Emperors
:أحد الأباطرة الأربعة أحمر الشعر شانكس
Looks like we'll meet again soon,
...يبدو أننا سنلتقي قريبًا
Luffy!
يا لوفي
So, your bounty fell. Not much we can do.
حسنٌ، ليس بيدنا حيلة بشأن انخفاضها
Cheer up, Luffy! Let me help in some way. Let's do what we can!
ابتهج يا لوفي سأساعدك ونبذل جهدنا لرفعها مجددًا
Do you want me to cook you something?
أتريدني أن أطهو لك الطعام؟
Yeah...
أجل
Wait just. One. Minute.
...لحظة من فضلكم
Look.
انظروا
100 thousand, 1 million, 10 million...
...مئة ألف، مليون، عشرة ملايين
100 milli—
...مئة مليون
Your bounty...
...المكافأة التي على رأسك
is 1.5 billion belly!
!هي مليار ونصف بيري
The world looks to the Reverie...
بينما يترقّب العالم مؤتمر ليفيلي
while the crew heads toward Wano.
يتجه الطاقم إلى بلاد وانو